Guide to the Irving Fisher Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- MICROFILM INVENTORY
  - Hygienic Essays, Vol. III, 1913 June 1 - 1917 December 31
    - Public health movement
      - Eugenics
        - The Importance of Hygiene for Eugenics: Address at 1st National Conf. on Race Betterment, separate reprint, 1914 (Box 6)
          - Reprint of same ( Christian Work and Evangelist ), 1914 (Box 6)
        - Eugenics: Foremost Plan of Human Redemption: Address at 2nd Natl. Conf. on Race Betterment ( Official Proceedings of Conf. ), 1915 (Box 6)
          - Extracts from same ( Call, New York), 1915 (Box 6)
        - Statement concerning Immigration after the War ( Social Service Review ), 1915 (Box 6)
        - Statement concerning Race Deterioration in America ( Beacon, Wichita, Kansas), 1916 (Box 6)
        - War, Immigration, Eugenics: Third Report of the Committee on Immigration, Amer. Genetic Ass. ( Journal of Heredity ), 1916 (Box 6)
          - Separate reprint of same, 1916 (Box 6)
      - Public Health in War Times
        - Tragedy of War one of Eugenics: Address before the Connecticut Research Association ( Greenwich Press ), 1915 (Box 6)
        - Empty Cradles Worst War Horror: Interview ( New York Times ), 1915 (Box 6)
        - Public Health in War Times: Address at the University of North Dakota ( Quarterly Journal of the University ), 1917 (Box 6)
          - Separate reprint of same, 1917 (Box 6)
          - Abstract of same ( Review of Reviews ), 1917 (Box 6)
          - Extracts from same ( Grand Forks Herald ), 1917 (Box 6)
          - Address at Mills College Based on same ( Union, Sacramento, Cal.), 1917 (Box 6)
        - Extracts from Mills College address ( Christian Advocate ), 1917 (Box 6)
          - Extracts from same ( Tribune, Oakland, Cal.), 1917 (Box 6)
        - The Health of the Nation in War Time: Address before Civic Club, Portland, Ore. ( Oregonian, Portland), 1917 (Box 6)
        - Address before Amer. Assoc. for Labor Legislation, extemporaneous remarks ( North American, Philadelphia, Pa.), 1917 (Box 6)
          - Extracts from same ( Public Ledger, Phila.), 1917 (Box 6)
          - Extracts from same ( North American, Phila.), 1917 (Box 6)
          - Abstracts from same, ( News, Sandy Creek, N.Y.), 1917 (Box 6)
    - Economics and health
      - Human Health as a National Asset: Address at Battle Creek Sanitarium ( Battle Creek Idea, Mich.), 1913 (Box 6)
      - Series of articles written for John Gun-Shannon ( Hartford Times ), 1914 (Box 6)
        - 1. What Tuberculosis Costs the Individual and the State, 1914 (Box 6)
        - 2. Value of the Nation's Lives, 1914 (Box 6)
        - 3. What Sickness and Death Cost the U.S. Each Year, 1914 (Box 6)
        - 4. The Value of Good Health and Suggestions for Securing It, 1914 (Box 6)
      - Statements quoted in "25th Anniversary Message of a Life Insurance Agent", 1916 (Box 6)
  - Hygienic Essays, Vol. IV (Cont. from Vol. III), 1913 June 1 - 1917 December 31
    - Health Insurance
      - 1916
        - The $90 Baby: Extracts from address before Mass. Legislature on Health Insurance Bill ( Denver News ) (Box 7)
        - The Money Value of Human Beings: Letter Explaining "The $90 Baby" from same address ( N.Y. Times ) (Box 7)
        - War is Teaching us not to Waste Human Life, Health Insurance Interview ( N.Y. Times (Box 7)
        - A Working Legislative Program for Health Insurance: Address before 3rd New England Conference on Tuberculosis ( Farmer ) (Box 7)
      - 1917
        - The Need for Health Insurance: Presidential Address before the American Association for Labor Legislation ( American Labor Legislation Review ) (Box 7)
          - Original separate reprint of same with corrections (Box 7)
          - Separate reprint of same (Box 7)
          - Full Report of same ( Boston Evening Transcript ) (Box 7)
          - Reprint ( New England Medical Gazette ) (Box 7)
          - Separate reprint of Medical Gazette art (Box 7)
          - Extracts from same ( Saturdays Chronicle, New Haven, Conn.) (Box 7)
          - Extracts from same ( Herald, Elmira, N.Y.) (Box 7)
        - Paper based on Presidential address: read before Medical Society of the County of New York ( N.Y. State Journal of Medicine ) (Box 7)
          - Extracts from same paper ( N.Y. Times ) (Box 7)
        - Address based on material from Presidential address: delivered at opening of Evans Memorial Lecture series ( Boston Globe ) (Box 7)
        - Extracts from address before N.Y. Society for the Relief of Widows and Orphans of Medical Men. Based on Presidential address ( N.Y. Evening Globe ) (Box 7)
        - Extracts from address before American Medical Association. Based on same ( N.Y. Call ) (Box 7)
          - Abstract of same address ( Official Program Scientific Assembly American Medical Association ) (Box 7)
        - Extracts from speech before Social Workers' Club, Rochester. Based on Presidential address ( Democratic Chronicle, Rochester) (Box 7)
        - Economic Losses from Sickness are Frightful. Statements quoted. ( Business Chronicle of the Pacific Northwest ) (Box 7)
        - Health Insurance: Address before Academy of Medicine, Toronto. (Canada Lancet) (Box 7)
        - Health Insurance: reprint from Connecticut State Board of Health Bulletin (Box 7)
        - For Health Insurance: Letter ( Boston Advertiser ) (Box 7)
        - Makes plea for Health Insurance: Extracts from address before Business Women's Club, Boston ( Journal, Boston) (Box 7)
        - Resolved that Health Insurance Should be Adopted by this State: Debate at the Ford Hall Foundation, Boston. ( Advertiser, Boston) (Box 7)
        - Health Insurance: Address before School Masters Assoc. of New York and Vicinity ( N.Y. Sun ) (Box 7)
        - Health Insurance: Article ( Star, Marion, O.) (Box 7)
        - Letter Concerning Connecticut Bill for Health Insurance ( Waterbury, Conn. Amer .) (Box 7)
        - Letter concerning statements of William G. Curtis on Health Insurance Bill drafted by American Association for Labor Legislations ( Free Press, Detroit) (Box 7)
          - Second Letter concerning same ( Free Press ) (Box 7)
        - Health Insurance for the Wage Earner: Article ( Insurance, N.Y.) (Box 7)
        - Reprint of same for distribution (Box 7)
        - Conserving Human Life: Statement on Health Insurance ( Pulitzer's Review ) (Box 7)
    - Tuberculosis
      - 1913
        - Ninth Annual Report of the New Haven County Anti-Tuberculosis Association concerning the work of the Gaylord Farm Sanatorium (Box 7)
      - 1914
        - Housing Related to Tuberculosis: Address to Chamber of Commerce, New Haven ( New Haven Journal Courier ) (Box 7)
        - Tenth Annual Report of the New Haven County Anti-Tuberculosis Association (Box 7)
          - Separate reprint. Review of the Ten Years' Work (Box 7)
        - Ten Years' Work at Gaylord Farm Sanatorium: Article ( Journal of the Outdoor Life ) (Box 7)
          - Separate reprint from same article (Box 7)
          - Extracts from same ( Journal, Lewiston, Me.) (Box 7)
      - 1915
        - How to Fight Tuberculosis: Article ( Good Health ) (Box 7)
          - Extracts from same ( Eagle, Reading, Pa.) (Box 7)
          - Reprint of same ( Spunk, Pa.) (Box 7)
        - Tuberculosis, Decreased Vitality and Impaired Powers Overcome: Article ( Association Men ) (Box 7)
    - Prohibition, Alcohol, and Tobacco
      - 1915
        - The Attitude of the College Man Towards Alcohol: Article ( Eli Book, Yale College) (Box 7)
          - Separate reprint of same (Box 7)
          - Reprint of same ( Montclarian, Montclair, N.J.) (Box 7)
        - Letter to Labor Leaders in regard to prohibition and labor ( The Boston Herald ) (Box 7)
          - Reprint of same letter with letter to Mr. W.F. Tilton ( Anti-Alcohol, Cambridge) (Box 7)
        - Extracts from letter to Mr. Tilton ( Boston Evening Record ) (Box 7)
        - Revised letter ( Boston Advertiser ) (Box 7)
          - Extract from same ( The Outlook ) (Box 7)
      - 1916
        - Reprint of "The Attitude of the College Man Toward Alcohol" ( North American Student ) (Box 7)
        - Reprint from North American Student ( Union Signal ) (Box 7)
          - Separate reprint (from Eli Book ) (Box 7)
        - Leaflet extracts based on "The Attitude of the College Man Towards Alcohol" ( Presbyterian Board of Temperance, Pittsburgh) (Box 7)
          - No. 87 "Facts for the Fight" (Box 7)
          - No. 88 "Alcohol vs. Brain Power" (Box 7)
          - No. 89 "The College Man Vs. Alcohol" (Box 7)
        - Extracts from Leaflet No. 88 ( Presbyterian Advance, Nashville, Tenn.) (Box 7)
        - What Shall we say of Tobacco? Article ( Boy Patriot, Cedar Rapids, Iowa) (Box 7)
        - Is the Tobacco Habit Injurious? Booklet (Box 7)
        - Extracts concerning Prohibition quoted from "Some Impending National Problems" ( Trades Union News ) (Box 7)
      - 1917
        - Quotations from "Is the Tobacco Habit Injurious?" ( Goodbody's Market Letter ) (Box 7)
        - Quotations from "The Attitude of the College Man Towards Alcohol" ( North American, Philadelphia) (Box 7)
        - Quotations from "The Attitude of the College Man Towards Alcohol" ( Union Signal ) (Box 7)
        - Liquor vs Bread: Letter ( Advertiser, Boston) (Box 7)
        - Letter on War Prohibition ( Public Ledger, Phil.) (Box 7)
        - Prohibition Must Come Unless War Ends Soon ( N.Y. Times Magazine ) (Box 7)
          - Extracts from same ( Saturday Chronicle, New Haven) (Box 7)
          - Extracts from same ( Spokesman Review, Spokane, Wash.) (Box 7)
        - Letter in answer to T.M. Gilmore's reply to "Prohibition Must Come Unless War Ends Soon" ( N.Y. Times ) (Box 7)
        - Letter answering a letter of T.M. Gilmore's ( Jersey Journal ) (Box 7)
        - Need for Prohibition in War Time: Address at Plymouth Church, Brooklyn ( Eagle, Brooklyn) (Box 7)
        - The case for War-Time Prohibition: Leaflet written for Committee on War Time Prohibition (Box 7)
        - Alcohol Greatly Needed for Manufacture of Munitions: Article Based on above leaflet ( Yale News ) (Box 7)
        - War Time Prohibition: Address before Civic Organizations of Philadelphia (Separate reprint) (Box 7)
          - Extracts from same ( North American, Phil.) (Box 7)
          - Extracts from same ( Evening Telegram, Phil.) (Box 7)
        - Extracts concerning Prohibition from "Public Health as a Social Movement" ( Reporter, Washington, Pa.) (Box 7)
        - Letter on War-Time Prohibition ( Survey, N.Y.) (Box 7)
        - Reply to Mr. Mark Mason ( Sunday Transcript, Phil.) (Box 7)
        - Noted Economists and Food Experts Call Attention to the Food-Stuffs Used in Liquor (War Prohibition Committee) (Box 7)
          - Extracts from same ( Commerce, Lincoln, Neb.) (Box 7)
          - Extracts from same ( Manufacturers' Record ) (Box 7)
        - How Much Food Conservation is Possible from War-Time Prohibition and How Greatly is it Needed ( Congressional Record ) (Box 7)
          - Separate reprint of same (Box 7)
          - Reprint of same ( News-Tribune, Detroit) (Box 7)
        - The U.S. Pays Two Billion to Get a Quarter Billion for Treasury (Publication of the Committee on War-Time Prohibition) (Box 7)
          - Reprint of same ( Business Chronicle of the Pacific Northwest ) (Box 7)
          - Extracts from same ( Piedmont, Greenville, S.C.) (Box 7)
          - Letter based on same ( Boston Advertiser ) (Box 7)
        - Alcohol vs Efficiency: Article (Man Power) (Box 7)
        - Introduction to Dr. Fisk's book on "Alcohol" quoted in (Literary Digest) (Box 7)
        - Congress to Pass Anti-Rum Bill: Article ( North American ) (Box 7)
        - National Prohibition: Interview ( Grand Forks Herald ) (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous
      - 1913
        - The Opportunities of the Invalid: Address at Battle Creek Sanitarium ( Medical Missionary ) (Box 7)
      - 1914
        - Reprint of same in Spanish (La Salud) (Box 7)
      - 1915
        - Statistics of Longevity: Paper Presented before the Second National Conference on Race Betterment ( Official Proceedings of the Conference ) (Box 7)
        - Letter Concerning Hygiene and the Medical Profession ( Profession of Medicine ) (Box 7)
      - 1916
        - The Mortality of our Public Men: Paper presented at the American Statistical Association ( Quarterly Publications of the Association ) (Box 7)
          - Separate reprint of same (Box 7)
          - Extracts from same (Bulletin, Norwich, Conn.) (Box 7)
      - 1917
        - Why is Spring Fever? ( Journal Sioux City, Iowa) (Box 7)
    - Early Publications from Previous Volumes
      - 1907
        - To Make Outdoor Sleeping Easy and Popular Interview ( N.Y. Times ) (Box 7)
      - 1908
        - Letter to the Committee of One Hundred ( American Health ) (Box 7)
      - 1909
        - Report as President of the American Health League ( American Health ) (Box 7)
      - 1911
        - How to Double Endurance by Diet: Article (Journal of the Outdoor Life) (Box 7)
      - 1912
        - Public Health Movement: Address before the Fourth Conservation Congress ( Proceedings of same ) (Box 7)
    - Publications Contained in Other Forms in Previous Volumes
      - 1909
        - Campaign for Improved Hygienic Conditions: address before Assoc. of Life Insurance Presidents ( Indicator, Detroit) (Box 7)
        - Extract from "Economic Aspect of Lengthening Human Life" ( Journal, Biddeford, Me.) (Box 7)
        - Extracts from address at Chautauqua, N.Y. on Improving Nation's Health ( Chautauqua Daily ) (Box 7)
        - Reprint in Spanish of "High Endurance on Low Proteid Diet" ( La Salud, Guanajuato, Mexico) (Box 7)
      - 1910
        - Address on "Insurance Companies and the Public Health" at Bretton Woods ( International Association of Accident Underwriters ) (Box 7)
        - Address before American Association for Study and Prevention of Infant Mortality, Baltimore ( Trans. 1st Annual Meeting, American Association for Study and Prevention of Infant Mortality ) (Box 7)
      - 1912
        - Extracts from "A New Method for Indicating Food Values" quoted in "The Construction of Dietaries" by Joseph Smyth, M.D. (Box 7)
      - 1914
        - Reprint of "The Influence of Flesh-Eating on Endurance" ( Yale Medical Journal ) (Box 7)
          - Reprint of same ( Journal of Scientific Physical Training ) (Box 7)
          - Separate reprint of same (Box 7)
        - Extract from "Graphic Method in Practical Dietetics," Life Extension Institute (Box 7)
        - Simple Rules for Right Living ( The Prudential ) (Box 7)
        - Rules of Individual Hygiene ( Business Service, Detroit, Mich.) (Box 7)
      - 1915
        - Practical Suggestions prepared for Bankers Health Commission, reprint of Rules of Hygiene ( American Bankers Association Journal ) (Box 7)
          - Reprint of same ( The Commercial West ) (Box 7)
        - Extracts from "Rules of Individual Hygiene" ( Argus, Middletown, N.Y.) (Box 7)
        - Alcohol To-Day ( Good Health, London, Engl.) (Box 7)
      - 1916
        - Extract from suggestions prepared for Bankers ( Index ) (Box 7)
        - Extracts from "Rules of Individual Hygiene ( Knickerbocker Press, Albany, N.Y.) (Box 7)
        - Extracts from "Economic Aspect of Lengthening Human Life" ( The Fra, East Aurora, N.Y.) (Box 7)
  - Hygienic Essays, Vol. V, 1918 January 1 - 1922 January 1
    - Public Health Movement
      - General
        - 1918
          - Address to Employees Tuberculosis Relief Association ( Journal-Courier, N.H.) (Box 7)
            - Same ( Registers, N.H. ) (Box 7)
        - 1919
          - Flu fight is indorsed by Professor Fisher ( Cleveland Press ) (Box 7)
          - Address at banquet of Life Extension Institute ( L.E.I. pamphlet ) (Box 7)
      - Individual and Domestic Hygiene
        - 1918
          - Fifteen Rules for Hygienic Living ( People's Popular Monthly ) (Box 7)
          - Spanish translation of "How to Live Long," in serial form ( El Commercial, San Jose, Costa Rica) (Box 7)
        - 1920
          - Extract from "How to Live" ( Junior Red Cross News ) (Box 7)
      - Eugenics
        - 1921
          - Impending Problems of Eugenics ( Scientific Monthly ) (Box 7)
            - Abstract of same ( Eugenical News ) (Box 7)
      - Public Health in War Times
        - 1918
          - Letter to N.Y. Evening Post on physical disability of soldiers ( N.Y. Evening Post ) (Box 7)
          - Address at Hartford City Club on What are we Fighting For ( Hartford Courant ) (Box 7)
          - Health and War ( American Labor Legislation Review ) (Box 7)
            - Separate reprint of same (Box 7)
            - Extracts from same ( American Journal of Public Health ) (Box 7)
            - The Lengthening of Human Life--in Retrospect and in Prospect, address before 3rd Race Betterment Conference, Battle Creek, 1928 Jan 5, reprinted from Proceedings of the Third Race Betterment Conference (Box 7)
            - Extracts from same (Box 7)
              - Paving Cutters' Journal (Box 7)
              - Age Herald, Birmingham, Ala. (Box 7)
              - Star Gazette, Elmira, N.Y. (Box 7)
              - Kansas City Star (Box 7)
            - Full report of "Health and War" ( Boston Herald ) (Box 7)
            - Extracts from same (Box 7)
              - N.Y. Tribune (Box 7)
              - Providence Tribune (Box 7)
              - Paper (Box 7)
              - Boston Daily Advertiser (Box 7)
              - Boston Daily Advertiser (Box 7)
              - N.Y. Sun (Box 7)
              - "Satisfying the Seven Fundamental Human Instincts" Independent (Box 7)
              - The Draper of Australasia (Box 7)
              - Current Opinion (Box 7)
              - Service (Box 7)
              - N.Y. Sun (Box 7)
              - Literary Digest (Box 7)
              - News, Toledo (Box 7)
              - Leader, Pittsburgh (Box 7)
            - Broadside sent out by Newspaper Enterprise Association based on "Health and War" (Box 7)
            - Reprint of same ( Times Union, Albany, N.Y.) (Box 7)
            - Extracts from same ( Wall St. Magazine ) (Box 7)
        - 1919
          - Extracts from same ( Watchman, Boston) (Box 7)
    - Health Insurance
      - 1918
        - Extract from "The Need for Health Insurance" ( Seymour Record, Seymour, Conn.) (Box 7)
        - Health Insurance Arousing Interest ( Free Press, Detroit) (Box 7)
        - Abstract of remarks on health insurance before Commission on Public Welfare ( Courant, Hartford, Conn.) (Box 7)
        - Statement to Newark Evening News in re adverse report of Society of Medical Jurisprudence (Box 7)
    - Prohibition, Alcohol, and Tobacco
      - 1918
        - Save 25 per cent to carry on the war ( Christian Register ) (Box 7)
        - War-time Prohibition (Report of Conference of League for Preventive Work) (Box 7)
        - Extracts from "Is the Tobacco Habit Injurious" ( School Bulletin, Portland, Ore.) (Box 7)
        - Shall War Finance be Sound or Unsound? ( Intercollegiate Statesman ) (Box 7)
        - Statement on Why Students should Support War Prohibition ( Intercollegiate Statesman ) (Box 7)
        - Extracts from "War-time Prohibition" ( Boston Globe ) (Box 7)
          - Extracts from same ( Bulletin of the Mass. Total Abstinence Society ) (Box 7)
        - Letter to N.H. Journal Courier (in re above statement) (Box 7)
        - Letter to N.H. Journal Courier (in re editorial April 16, 1918) (Box 7)
        - Interview in N.Y. Tribune in re prohibition (Box 7)
        - Reply to Mr. Sears' letter of 1918 Apr 19 ( N.H. Journal Courier ) (Box 7)
        - Statement on prohibition amendment in answer to Prof. Doughty of Williams College ( Evening Bulletin, Philadelphia) (Box 7)
        - Extracts from address before War-time Prohibition Association of Pennsylvania ( Public Ledger, Phila.) (Box 7)
        - Extracts from "War-Time Prohibition" ( Christian Endeavor World ) (Box 7)
        - Letter to N.Y. Tribune in answer to letter of T.M. Gilmore (Box 7)
        - Abstract of prohibition address at annual convention of Episcopal Diocese of Connecticut (Hartford Times) (Box 7)
          - Same ( Journal Courier ) (Box 7)
          - Same ( N.H. Register ) (Box 7)
        - Extracts from "War-time Prohibition" ( National Enquirer ) (Box 7)
        - Abstract of prohibition address at annual convention of Episcopal Diocese of Connecticut ( Living Church ) (Box 7)
        - Statement concerning brewers and German-American organization in answer to Whidden Graham' s questions in 1918 Apr 27 issue of N.H. Journal Courier (Box 7)
          - Separate reprint of same (Box 7)
        - Letter to N.H. Journal Courier in answer to William H. Sears' (Box 7)
        - Is Tobacco Essential? ( Forum ) (Box 7)
        - Extracts from interview in N.Y. Tribune on prohibition ( Journal, Minneapolis) (Box 7)
        - Tobacco ( No-Tobacco Journal ) (Box 7)
        - Letter to Senator Henry L. Myers in re bill closing saloons around coal mines ( Congressional Record ) (Box 7)
        - Extracts of address before organization meeting of the New Haven Committee for National Prohibition ( Connecticut Patriot ) (Box 7)
          - Same ( Journal Courier ) (Box 7)
        - Reprint of address before organization meeting of the New Haven Committee for National Prohibition re Mr. Taft on prohibition ( Connecticut Citizen ) (Box 7)
          - Extracts from same ( Press Bulletin No. 114 of Conn. Temperance Union ) (Box 7)
      - 1919
        - Is the Tobacco Habit Injurious? New edition published by Y.M.C.A. (Box 7)
        - Can Prohibition Drive out Drink? ( The Independent ) (Box 7)
          - Separate reprint of same (Box 7)
          - Reprint of same ( North American, Phila.) (Box 7)
        - Extracts from letter to Senator Harry Leonard in re Connecticut's ratifying prohibition ( Republican, Springfield, Mass.) (Box 7)
          - Same ( New Haven Union ) (Box 7)
        - Extracts from remarks by I.F. in introducing Dr. Wilbur F. Crafts at First Methodist Church ( N.H. Register ) (Box 7)
        - Letter to Journal Courier in reply to editorial (Box 7)
        - Reprint of "Can Prohibition Drive Out Drink?" ( Christian Work ) (Box 7)
          - Extracts from same (Box 7)
            - National Enquirer (Box 7)
            - Patriot Phalanx, Indianapolis (Box 7)
            - American Issue, Westerville, Ohio (Box 7)
          - Card quoting from same (Issued by Mass. Anti-Saloon League) (Box 7)
        - Extracts from "War-time Prohibition" ( Virginian, Richmond) (Box 7)
        - The Significance of the Anti-Alcohol Movement (reprint of Natl. Conference of Social Work) (Box 7)
        - Extracts from same (Public Ledger, Phila.) (Box 7)
      - 1920
        - Extracts from "Will Prohibition Drive Out Drink" ( Intercollegiate Statesman, Chicago) (Box 7)
        - Statement re prohibition (Pamphlet issued by Internatl. Reform Bureau, 26th Anniv., Washington, D.C.) (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous
      - 1919
        - The High Mortality of Public Men (New York Tribune et al.) (Box 7)
          - Extracts from same ( News Bee, Toledo et al.) (Box 7)
    - Publications Contained in Other Forms in Previous Volumes
      - 1917
        - Reprint of letter in answer to T.M. Gilmore's reply to "Prohibition Must Come Unless War Ends Soon" (Box 7)
        - Extracts from "Is the Tobacco Habit Injurious?" ( No-Tobacco Journal ) (Box 7)
        - Extracts from address on Health Insurance before Academy of Medicine, Toronto ( Medical Journal, Montreal) (Box 7)
  - Health Essays, Vol. VI: "General", 1924 - 1931
    - Omitted from previous volumes:
      - Address at 4th National Conservation Congress, Oct 1912 (Box 7)